Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 25: Memorandam on University research Programs in the Field of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Committee on Labor Market research of the Social Science research Council. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Business Research Projects - 1941, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By US Department of Commerce, Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Survey of Business research Projects at University, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 28: tentatives Outlines and Summaries of Studies in Progress, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By National Recovery Administration, Division of Review. labor Studies and Trade Practice Studies. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations: What's Wrong With the System?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Allan Flanders. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rubber Industry of the United States, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By P. W. Barker; E. G Holt. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Do the Seniority Rights of Employees Survive an Expired Contract?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Eugene Hoffman. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Seniority in Industrial relations: A Selected List of References, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Laura Thompson. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Union's Position on the Merit-Ability-Seniority Issue, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Brendan Sexton. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Seniority and the Negro Worker, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Robert Weaver. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Seniority, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By NAM Employee relations Division. A Review for Management use in Appraising Seniority Practices in light of Current Conditions. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Seniority Problems During Demobilization and Reconversion, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Industrial relations Section, Princeton University. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Saving Plans, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By John Tinsley. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: After a Life of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Human Service for Retirees. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Research Papers 4 Productivity and restrictive Labor Practices, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employer's Association. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Memorandum on University research Programs in the Field of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Committee on Labor Market Research. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Memorandum on University Research Programs in the Fiels of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Memorandum on University Research Programs in the Field of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Memorandum on universitu Research Programs on the Field of labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By John Turnbull. A Research Planning Memorandum. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Report of the Human Relations in Industry Conference, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By Report of the Human Relations in Industry Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Productivity team Technique, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    By P. H. Cook. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Beware of Seniority Provisions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Industrial Commentaries. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Seniority Principle in Union-Management Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Frederick Harbison. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Seniority Principle in Employment Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Industrial Relations Section, Princeton University. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Study of Seniority in Collective Bargaining Agreements, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Henry Metcalf. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Seniority in the Automobile Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Philip Trezise. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Seniority, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    By Group Insurance Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Seniority Problem, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Report of Survey on Shortage of Skilled men in Metal Working Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By American Society of Tool Engineers. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Skilled Work Force, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By James P. Mitchell. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Skilled Labor Force, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By United States Department of Labor, Bureau of Apprenticeship. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Shortage of Skilled Manpower, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Henry Thole. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Skilled Workers for Defense Industries, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Charles Slocombe. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Shortage of Critical Skills, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By Martin Packman. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Wanted: Skilled Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    By National Industrial Conference Board. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: War and Post-War Social Security, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Arthur Altmeyer; William Haber; I. S. Falk; Robert Watt; Smith Simpson; John Corson; Osvald Stein; Clinton Golden. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Beveridge Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Methods of Clearance Between Unemployment Compensation and Relief Agencies, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Arthur Jacobs. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Social Security in America, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Beveridge Report in Brief, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Beveridge, Sir William. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Social Security: Challenge to Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Neil Jacoby; Maynar Krueger; Clyde White. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Influence of Plant Size on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Sherrill Cleland. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Insurance for All and Everything, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    By Ronald Davison. Item is in English.
- Box 2, Folder (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Problems, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Farrell Dobbs. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Socialism in America, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Why Kill the Goode?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Sherman Rogers. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Public Ownership Here and Abroad, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Harry Laidler. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Which Road for American Workers, Socialist or Communist?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By Debate: Norman Thomas vs Earl Browder. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Worker as a Personality, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    By S. Kavcic. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Dispute Settlement in the Public Sector: Selected References, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Pickets at City Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By The Twentieth Century Fund. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Dispute Settlement in the Public Sector, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Thomas P. Gilroy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Emergency Disputes - Is There a Solution?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Research Papers 2 (Part 1): Disputes Procedures in British Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By A. I. Marsh. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Dispute Settlement Procedures in Five Western European Countries, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Benjamin Aaron. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Disputes and Their Settlement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Tadashi Hanami. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Work Stoppages and Teachers: History and Prospect, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Ronald W. Glass. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dismissal Compensation and the War Economy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Everett D. Hawkins. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Dismissal Compensation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By J. Douglas Brown; Everett D. Hawkins. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Conference Board Reports: Severance Pay Plans, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By National Industrial Conference Board, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Selected Bibliography - Dismissal Compensation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Selected Bibliography - Dismissal Compensation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. February 4, 1938. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Dismissal Wage: November 1954, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Cornell University, Industrial and Labor Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Dismissal Compensation: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Dismissal Compensation: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Severance Policies for Non-Administrative Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Dartnell Corp. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Severance Policies Non-Administrative Employees, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Thomas H. Bowman. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Severance Compensation Policies and Practices 1952, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By American Management Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Severance Compensation Policies and Practices 1952, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By American Management Association. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Severance Compensation Policies and Practies 1952, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By American Management Association. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Research and Information: Severance Pay Practices, Results of a Survey, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Standard Practice Instruction: Termination of Exempt Salaried Employees - Separation and Vacation Pay, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Solar Aircraft Company. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Cost-of-Living Escalator Clauses and Inflation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By H. M. Douty. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Progress Sharing at American Motors: A Comprehensive View of Profit Sharing in the Automobile Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By I. B. Helburn. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Cost Reduction Sharing Plans, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By J. A. McCormick. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: How Kaiser Steel Corporation's Long Range Sharing Plan Works, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Construction Industry Cost Effectiveness Project, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By University of Michigan. Organization/author unknown. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Bargaining Structure in Construction: Problems and Prospects, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Negotiating the Construction Code, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Building Trades Department of AFL; Solomon Barkin. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industrial Relations in the Construction Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Gordon W. Bertram; Sherman J. Maisel. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Relations in the Construction Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By William Haber; Harold M. Levinson. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Construction Worker in the United States, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Productivity Trends in the Construction Industry: A Comparative International Review, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Restrictive Practices of the Building Trades, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By The Associated General Contractors of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Construction Industry Selected References 1960-1969, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Jurisdictional Problems in Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By The Business Roundtable. Letter addressed to G. S. Birrell attached to the front. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Wage Guidelines: The Negative Impact Upon Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Contractors Mutual Association. February 23, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Collective Bargaining in the Construction Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Illinois University, Industry of Labor and Industrial Relations. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The GAO on Davis-Bacon: A Fatally Flawed Study, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Center to Protect Workers' Rights. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Unionized Construction Workers Are More Productive, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Steven G. Allen. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: In Defense of Davis-Bacon, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: More Construction for the Money, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By The Business Roundtable. A Construction Industry Cost Effectiveness Project Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Exclusive Jurisdiction in Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Impact of Local Union Politics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Constraints Imposed by Collective Bargaining Agreements, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Contractor Supervision in Unionized Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Construction Labor Motivation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Labor Supply Information, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Absenteeism and Turnover, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: First and Second Level Supervisory Training, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Scheduled Overtime Effect on Construction Projects, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By The Business Roundtable. A Rountable Report. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Contractual Arrangements, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Improving Construction Safety Performance, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Construction Training Through Vocational Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Government Limitations on Training Innovations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Training Problems in Open Shop Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Measuring Productivity in Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Administration and Enforcement of Building Codes and Regulations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Modern Management Systems, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Construction Technology Needs and Priorities, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Technological Progress in the Construction Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Integrating Construction Resources and Technology into Engineering, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Subjourneymen in Union Construction, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Local Labor Practices, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Management Education and Academic Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Prison Industries, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By U.S. Department of Commerce. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Effective Collective Bargaining Revised, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    By David J. Saposs; Lyle Cooper. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Coordinated Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining in Transition, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By Guy Farmer. 1. Coalition Bargaining and Union Power. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Organized Labor's Use of Coalition Bargaining: The Noose Gets Tighter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    By M. R. Lefkoe. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Industrial Disputes and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By William H. Davis; Paul H. Douglas; William M. Leiserson; Donald R. Richberg; Lewis B. Schwellenbach. Series of addresses. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wage Determination and the Economics of Liberalism, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By E. Wight Bakke; John T. Dunlop; Fritz Machlup; Felix Morley; Jacob Viner; Leo Wolman. Series of addresses; January 11, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Unionization of Profressional Engineers and Chemists, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By Herbert R. Northrup. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Industry-Wide Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By Leo Wolman. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Role of Collective Bargaining in a Competitive Society, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    By E. Wight Bakke. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What's Wrong With Collective Bargaining?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Rutgers University. Fourth Annual Labor-Management Conference; May 13, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Relationship Between Collective Bargaining and Personnel Administration, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Multi-Employer Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Jules Backman. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Mature Collective Bargaining: Prospects and Problems, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Anne P. Cook. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By E. W. Mounce; Robley D. Stevens. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Factors in Successful Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By U.S. Senate. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Basic Approaches to Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By John S. Bugas. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Scope of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    By Walter L. Daykin. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The UAW 1958 Bargaining Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By UAW. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining or Monopoly, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Today, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Proceedings of the Conference on Current Issues in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Mark K. Fitzgerald; John J. Broderick. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Views Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Joseph A. Beirne. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Public Issues and Practical Problems in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By University of Michigan; Wayne State University. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Role of Collective Bargaining in the Economy, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By John T. Dunlop. Reproduced in pamphlet form for the United Glass and Ceramic Workers Union by Leland Beard. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Union Decisions in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Robert R. France. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Research in Collective Bargaining: An Evaluation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Joseph Shister. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Collective Barganing: Problems and Prospects, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Princeton University, Industrial Relations Section. Selected References (bibliography). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Use of Corporate Financial Statements and Related Data by Organized Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Wilbur F. Pillsbury. Indiana Business Report No. 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor Relations - The Practical View, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Georges Laverdure. September 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: An Essay on Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Thomas C. Schelling. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Non-Wage Aspects of Collective Bargaining: Effects on Productivity, Labor Mobility and Economic Growth, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    By Jack Stieber. September 30, 1959. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Justice on the Job, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: The Future of Collective Bargaining in the United States, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Richard A. Lester. May 10, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: General Electric's 1963 Negotiations: What About "Intervention"?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: The Future of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By William Gomberg. Magazine/Journal; January 20, 1962; "pp. 51-61" written on the front. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Case for Free Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Earl R. Bramblett. February 16, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By President's Advisory Committee on Labor-Management Policy; John F. Kennedy. Report to the President. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Outlook for Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By C. E. French. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Free and Responsible Collective Bargaining and Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By President's Advisory Committee on Labor- Management Policy. Taken from the Report to the President. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Free and Responsible Collective Bargaining and Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By President's Advisory Committee on Labor- Management Policy; John F. Kennedy. May 1, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box 3, Folder (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Centralized Information Service in Industrial Relations: A Feasibility Study, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By University of Michigan; Cornell University. Joint proposal by University of Michigan and Cornell University. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Feasibility Study Proposal, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By Louis Ferman; J. Gormly Miller. No official title. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Feasibility Study Report, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By University of Michigan; Wayne State University; Cornell University. No official title. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Appendix A: "Core" Journals and Serials, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By University of Michigan; Wayne State University; Cornell University. Series of charts from the Feasibility Study. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Appendix A: "Core" Journals and Serials, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By University of Michigan; Wayne State University; Cornell University. Series of charts from the Feasibility Study; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Summary of Results for Appendix A, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By University of Michigan; Wayne State University; Cornell University. No official title; part of the Feasibility Study. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Correspondences Regarding the Committee of University Industrial Relations Librarians Newsletter, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By Gordon C. Barhydt. Series of correspondences between Gordon Barhydt and various university librarians. Item is in English.